JAMES KIELLAND

425-971-7140

Profile

1115 Rainier Ave. #415

Everett, WA 98201

james.kielland@gmail.com High level digital media skills. Excellent customer service. Call center supervisory and training experience. Strong social media skills. Telephone sales. Ability to do heavy physical work with careful accuracy. And I can drive a stand-up forklift, too.

Skills

Digital Photography Image Editing Video Editing

Cashier **Customer Service** Call Center Supervision

Warehouse Stand-up Forklift Telephone Sales

Experience

Lee Arnold System of Real Estate — August 2018 to October 2018 Served in telephone sales of educational products for real estate investors with an emphasis on those doing fix and flips. Worked to determine customer's current situation and offer the right training to get them where they wanted to be.

Freedom eCommerce; Lynwood, Washington — May 2018 to August 2018 Telephone sales of complete e-commerce (website) solutions. Demonstrated strength in qualifying and committing the prospects for packages in the \$5000 to \$10,000 price range.

FedEx Ground; Auburn, Washington — November 2016 to March 2017 Unload and load of FedEx package delivery trucks. Capable of hard physical work that requires high attention to detail.

Amazon Fulfillment; Kent, Washington — March 2016 to September 2016 Worked in Amazon's fast-paced and demanding order fulfillment operations, including product stow and forklift operations. Consistently in the top 1% in terms of Amazon's demanding productivity markers.

Freelance Photographer — 2006-2013

High level skills in landscape, sports, candid, and event photography. My photography appeared on the front cover of the largest circulating arts publication in the world, Artists and Illustrators, Sept 2011 edition. Samples of my photography can be easily found with a simple Google image search on my name.

Liquid Design — 2001-2006

Supervised customer service for e-commerce, working with personnel who used English as a second language and refining their abilities to provide customer service via email/chat in English. Also supervised fraud detection and prevention.

Education

Renton Technical College, Renton, Washington — High School Diploma, 1989